NYLES EBBESEN SENIOR WEB ENGINEER

§ live:.cid.b45e8530ac5c3cb9

github.com/prowebdever

Copenhagen, Denmark

About Me

Seasoned experts with **5+** years of experience in the web & blockchain development and rich knowledge from low-level to high-level languages.

Proficient in developing full stack web applications across multiple platforms using best programming languages for web development like HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Angular, Vue, Typescript, PHP, Ruby, Python, Java, NodeJS and Solidity.

Rich experience in implementing of **AWS** solutions and strong understanding of different development methodologies such as **Agile** and **TDD**.

Work Experiences

ELANIIN

Web3 Developer | 03/2021 - 08/2022

- o Developed a web-based application using 100% React JS
- o Strongly typed coding using **ES6** features and **Typescript** for 15% better visuals.
- Responsible for developing the **UI pages** using **Angular**6, **HTML5**, **CSS3**, **JavaScript** and **Bootstrap**.
- o Coded extensively using JavaScript frameworks by implementing MVC architecture.
- Worked on design, implementation and modifying the Python code, PostgreSQL database schema on the back end, increasing efficiency by 41%.
- Actively played the role of an **Agile** Programmer and followed **TDD** concepts to get high 13% effect.
- o Worked the **backend** by using **Node JS**, **Express** and **MongoDB** for 6+ months.
- o Developed **frontend** by using **AngularJS** and **JavaScript**.
- Have worked on AWS to integrate the server-side and client-side code, saving company \$2,000+ monthly.
- o Participated in developing the **smart contract**, which took me 8 months.
- o Built 3 reusable **cross-chain libraries**
- o Improved data structures to solve 3 serious issues and ease the work of the dev team

LIVATEK

Web Developer | 08/2018 - 01/2021

- Worked on React.JS components, Forms, Events, Keys, Router, Animations and Redux concept for 3+ months.
- o Developed Single Page Application using Angular JS in just 30 minutes.

- Developed the web component using HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, j Query, Redux and ReactJS to increase target audience engagement by 8%.
- o **Collaborated** with designers and performance team on designing updates to sites and blogs, improving user experience by **39%**.
- o Involved in writing **SQL Queries** and **Stored Procedures**, increasing processing effectiveness by **21%**.
- o Test RESTful design by using 60% **Postman**.
- **Communicated and worke**d with internal departments including managers, sales, customer service, project managers for 6+ months.
- o I have used **GIT** for over 5 years for version control system and code management.
- o Found and fixed over **70 bugs**, increasing security and usability
- Working on the formation and maintenance of innovate blockchain technology, and conducting expert market research
- Gaming platform over Ethereum blockchain using ERC 721

Education

Technical university of denmark | 2015-2018

Bachelor of Applied Science(Computer Science)

Skills

Pro	ogramming Langu	lages					
0	C/C++/C#	0	TypeScript	0	Go	0	React
0	CSS	0	Python	0	Java	0	NodeJS
0	JavaScript	0	Ruby	0	PHP	0	HTML5
Frameworks							
0	Express.js	0	Django	0	Spring	0	React.js
0	Laravel	0	Angular	0	Vue.js	0	ASP.NET
Cloud Platform							
0	AWS	0	Azure				
Database							
0	MySQL	0	PostgreSQL	0	MongoDB	0	SQLite
nterests							
0	Reading Books	0	Tennis	0]	Football		Making new Triends